# JACK O'CONNOR

### FULL STACK DEVELOPER

#### SKILLS Python

Python3

UnitTest/TDD

Flask

OpenCV

Django

MySQL

**SQLlite** 

Bcrypt

Ajax and APIs

Amazon EC2

Gunicorn

Wsg

C#

C# Language Fundamentals

.NET Core runtime/standard library

ASP.NET Core MVC

Dapper

**Entity Framework** 

MySQL

Postgresql

Ajax

MEAN

es5

es6

typescript

Node

**Express** 

npm

socket.io

Angular

AJAX

MongoDB

NoSQL

Mongoose

Bcrypt

Redis

Postman

HTML

**JavaScript** 

CSS

CONTACT

708-828-4238

jackoconnorthethird@yahoo.com

Github https://github.com/jackoconnorthethird

LinkedIn https://www.linkedin.com/in/jackoconnoriii/



#### SUMMARY

I am a full stack developer specializing in Python, C#, and MEAN. I am a hard-working professional with experience and proven success in both sales and project management. Upon discovering a passion for coding, I leveraged my skills in communication, creativity, and ability to learn through adversity while staying calm under pressure. I honed my programming skills at Coding Dojo. I am searching for the right company and culture to grow with while utilizing my skills and passion.



#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### Financial Adviser | Lakeshore Wealth Strategies | 5/2018 - 1/2019

- Formed personalized strategies for each client
- Networked and grew my own book of business
- · Assisted clients in all aspects financial health

#### Project Engineer | Kelso-Burnett | 7/2016 - 3/2018

- Helped manage projects ranging from 500K to 10 million dollars
- Ensured the electricians and inventory was managed effectivly
- · Spearheaded communications with office and the field



## EDUCATION CODING DOJO

Triple Belt Certification 2019-2019

#### **EASTERN ILLINOIS UNIVERSITY**

Bachelor of Science

2012-2014